You once said something to me,
لقد قلت لي شيئًا ذات مرة ،
which is still fresh in my memory.
التي لا تزال حاضرة في ذاكرتي.
She said,
قالت ،
if you don't want to betray me,
إذا كنت لا تريد أن تخونني ،
You shouldn't trust anyone.
لا يجب أن تثق بأحد.
Miss Shi.
ملكة جمال شي.
Shi Miaomiao,
شي مياومياو ،
Miaomiao,
مياومياو ،
Got it
فهمتك
Just ignore me.
فقط تجاهلني.
If Shi Miaomiao has any conspiracy later,
إذا كان لدى شي مياومياو أي مؤامرة لاحقًا ،
you can take Pan Jun with you.
يمكنك اصطحاب Pan Jun معك.
They wouldn't dare to do anything to me.
لن يجرؤوا على فعل أي شيء بي.
It's impossible for us
هذا مستحيل بالنسبة لنا
to run one by one, Yanyun,
لتشغيل واحدًا تلو الآخر ، يانيون ،
Let's get out of here
فلنخرج من هنا
alive today.
على قيد الحياة اليوم.
or
أو
Let's die here together.
دعونا نموت هنا معا.
They're here.
انهم هنا.
Brother Pan,
الأخ بان ،
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
Are you really coming?
هل انت قادم حقا
I told you to protect the secret treasure,
قلت لك أن تحمي الكنز السري ،
but you just turned a deaf ear
لكنك فقط أدرت أذنًا صماء
to my words when they asked you to take it,
لكلماتي عندما طلبوا منك أن تأخذه ،
Are you hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
Shi Miaomiao,
شي مياومياو ،
Yan Yun,
يان يون ،
Save these words for later. What about
احفظ هذه الكلمات لوقت لاحق.  ماذا عن
the secret treasure?
الكنز السري؟
Miaomiao didn't hurt me,
Miaomiao لم يؤذيني ،
but it's hard to explain that there's a misunderstanding.
لكن من الصعب توضيح أن هناك سوء فهم.
She poisoned you and didn't hurt you.
لقد سممتك ولم تؤذيك.
If I don't say so,
إذا لم أقل ذلك ،
how can you willingly
كيف يمكنك عن طيب خاطر
hand over the secret treasure?
تسليم الكنز السري؟
Can you stop making a fire here?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن إشعال النار هنا؟
Let me tell you, Yanyun,
دعني أخبرك ، يانيون ،
I was a guest at the AsiaInfo Club.
كنت ضيفًا في نادي AsiaInfo Club.
You eat well and drink spicy food every day,
تأكل جيدًا وتشرب طعامًا حارًا كل يوم ،
and there are beauties throwing themselves at you?
وهنالك جميلات يرمون أنفسهن عليك؟
Shut up!
اخرس!
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
Listen to me,
استمع لي،
you three.
لك ثلاث.
Yan Yun
يان يون
Shi Miaomiao,
شي مياومياو ،
you should know that
عليك ان تعلم ذلك
my master was a native gentleman Feng Wanchun
كان سيدي رجلًا محليًا فينج وان تشون
back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
He also went to Mount Ba Men.
كما ذهب إلى جبل با مين.
He has a mission,
لديه مهمة ،
Tell me to finish the lunch
قل لي أن أنهي الغداء
Remember,
يتذكر،
I, the Zerg, have never betrayed anyone.
أنا الزرج لم أخن أحداً قط.
Water system gentleman Shi Shiyu,
نظام المياه السيد شي شيو ،
taking the lead and facing death unflinchingly,
أخذ زمام المبادرة ومواجهة الموت بلا تردد ،
If there is a river system,
إذا كان هناك نظام نهر ،
we should resolve the conflict,
يجب علينا حل الصراع ،
The five clans work together,
العشائر الخمس تعمل معًا ،
don't let the treasure fall into the hands of others.
لا تدع الكنز يقع في أيدي الآخرين.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
On behalf of the elders of the four departments,
نيابة عن شيوخ الأقسام الأربعة ،
I apologize to the river system.
أعتذر لنظام النهر.
If you want to kill or scratch, just do as you please.
إذا كنت تريد القتل أو الخدش ، فقط افعل ما يحلو لك.
What a joke. Do you think
يالها من مزحة.  هل تعتقد
I'll let you go
سأدعك تذهب
if you do this?
إذا قمت بذلك؟
Then my mother,
ثم والدتي ،
as well as the whole water system,
وكذلك نظام المياه بالكامل ،
How are you going to repay it?
كيف ستسددها؟
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
Miaomiao,
مياومياو ،
Look,
نظرة،
I told you the same thing,
قلت لك نفس الشيء
as long as you're willing to let go of your hatred and live a normal life,
طالما أنك على استعداد للتخلي عن كراهيتك والعيش حياة طبيعية ،
We can all give our lives for you.
يمكننا جميعًا أن نقدم حياتنا من أجلك.
This is our sincerity.
هذا هو صدقنا.
Shi Miaomiao,
شي مياومياو ،
I'm willing to give my life to my life.
أنا على استعداد لإعطاء حياتي لحياتي.
I only want to ask you one thing.
أريد فقط أن أسألك شيئًا واحدًا.
The Zerg treasure,
كنز الزرج
must not fall into the hands of the Yaxin Club.
يجب ألا يقع في أيدي نادي Yaxin.
Come with us to Mount Ba Men.
تعال معنا إلى جبل با مين.
Let's go find our father.
دعنا نذهب للعثور على والدنا.
Go find the truth.
اذهب واكتشف الحقيقة.
But I have no choice.
لكن ليس لدي خيار.
For so many years,
لسنوات عديدة ،
I've endured humiliation and lived in Toyo,
لقد تحملت الإذلال وعشت في تويو ،
Stay dormant and endure in Yaxin,
ابق في سبات وتحمل في Yaxin ،
I have no way out.
ليس لدي مخرج.
No.
رقم.
You have,
لديك،
you still have me.
لازلت معك.
With Yan Yun and Ziwu,
مع يان يون وزيوو ،
we can protect you.
يمكننا حمايتك.
Fire can repel insects
يمكن للنار أن تصد الحشرات
and control animals. Earth can use all kinds of poisons.
وضبط الحيوانات.  يمكن للأرض استخدام جميع أنواع السموم.
Good health.
صحة جيدة.
My department of wood
قسم الخشب بلدي
can save lives,
يمكن أن تنقذ الأرواح ،
If it's a difficult disease,
إذا كان مرضًا صعبًا ،
we'll give you
سنعطيك
an explanation for the water system.
شرح لنظام المياه.
And didn't you also tell me?
ألم تخبرني أيضًا؟
Trust me as long as I come with you.
صدقني ما دمت أتيت معك.
Now I'm here with you.
الآن أنا هنا معك.
Trust me, okay?
صدقني ، حسنًا؟
Don't go back.
لا ترجعوا.
We can leave together.
يمكننا المغادرة معا.
Don't go back to Matsui.
لا تعود إلى ماتسوي.
Why didn't you take action?
لماذا لم تتخذ أي إجراء؟
Where was Miss?
اين كانت انسة؟
Shi Miaomiao,
شي مياومياو ،
you didn't want to let us go from the beginning.
لم ترغب في السماح لنا بالرحيل من البداية.
Yan Yun
يان يون
Miss Shi,
ملكة جمال شي ،
Mr. Matsui is here.
السيد ماتسوي هنا.
He urged you to get the secret treasure as soon as possible.
حثك على الحصول على الكنز السري في أسرع وقت ممكن.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
how many people did he bring?
كم شخص أحضر؟
Come out,
يخرج،
you tell him,
أخبره،
This is my family matter,
هذه مسألة عائلتي ،
and I have to avenge it myself.
ولا بد لي من الانتقام من ذلك بنفسي.
Ask him to give me more time.
اطلب منه أن يمنحني المزيد من الوقت.
Miss Shi,
ملكة جمال شي ،
15 minutes. I only need 15 minutes.
15 دقيقة.  أنا فقط بحاجة إلى 15 دقيقة.
Let them all go.
دعهم جميعا يذهبون.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
I'll get you out of here.
سوف أخرجك من هنا.
Before I find out the truth,
قبل أن أكتشف الحقيقة ،
I won't kill you.
لن اقتلك.
Follow me.
اتبعني.
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
Wait.
انتظر.
Give me some time.
إمنحني بضع الوقت.
I'll be right back.
سأعود حالا.
Miss Luo is here.
الآنسة لوه هنا.
Mr. Matsui,
السيد ماتسوي ،
long time no see,
وقت طويل لا رؤية،
Boss Jin heard that Yaxin
سمع بوس جين أن ياكسين
will do his best to encircle the Zerg tonight.
سيبذل قصارى جهده لتطويق الزرج الليلة.
As it happens,
كما يحدث،
Yaxin Pharmaceutical also wants to get it back,
تريد شركة Yaxin Pharmaceutical أيضًا استعادتها ،
The subject infected with Yersinia pestis,
الموضوع المصاب يرسينيا بيستيس ،
Miss Luo, don't worry.
آنسة لوه ، لا تقلق.
The Zerg
الزرج
can't leave this warehouse at all.
لا يمكن مغادرة هذا المستودع على الإطلاق.
No one is allowed to shoot tonight.
لا أحد مسموح له بإطلاق النار الليلة.
Boss Jin has an order.
بوس جين لديه أمر.
The experimental body Ziwu,
الجسم التجريبي Ziwu ،
We have to catch them alive,
علينا القبض عليهم أحياء ،
Yes.
نعم.
Search
يبحث
the battle
المعركة
and start searching carefully.
وابدأ البحث بعناية.
Don't let go of any corner.
لا تترك أي ركن.
Bro,
أخ،
Not good.
غير جيد.
It's the fragrance.
إنه العطر.
-Run! -Let's go! Everyone, get out!
-يركض!  -هيا بنا!  الجميع ، اخرجوا!
My Lady,
سيدتي،
what's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Someone lit some incense inside,
أشعل أحدهم بعض البخور بالداخل ،
and all the Zerg escaped.
وهرب كل الزرج.
Where is Miss Shi?
اين الانسة شي؟
No, I didn't see Miss Shi.
لا ، لم أر الآنسة شي.
Close the front and back exits immediately. Yes,
أغلق المخارج الأمامية والخلفية على الفور.  نعم،
come with me,
تعال معي،
They came
أتوا
prepared.
أعدت.
Why hasn't Ziwu come out yet?
لماذا لم يخرج Ziwu بعد؟
Let's go!
هيا بنا!
Matsui's men will surround this place soon.
سيحيط رجال ماتسوي بهذا المكان قريبًا.
I released Ye Lan Xiang,
أطلقت سراح يي لان شيانغ ،
but it won't last long.
لكنها لن تدوم طويلا.
They have a car. We can't outrun him.
لديهم سيارة.  لا يمكننا تجاوزه.
Let's go!
هيا بنا!
Come with us.
تعال معنا.
They won't let you go.
لن يسمحوا لك بالرحيل.
If you don't leave, I won't leave either.
إذا لم ترحل ، فلن أغادر أيضًا.
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
ماذا تفعل؟  هل أنت مجنون؟
Don't dawdle.
لا تتوانى.
No one can leave
لا أحد يستطيع المغادرة
if you don't leave. Let's go.
إذا لم ترحل.  هيا بنا.
Go after him!
اذهب ورائه!
It's almost dawn. We need to get out of the city.
اقترب الفجر.  نحن بحاجة للخروج من المدينة.
Strange,
غريب،
no one dares to stop us on the way.
لا أحد يجرؤ على إيقافنا في الطريق.
Are you afraid that we might hurt Mrs. Matsui?
هل تخشى أن نؤذي السيدة ماتسوي؟
She's not Mrs. Matsui at all.
إنها ليست السيدة ماتسوي على الإطلاق.
The name of her husband and wife with Matsui is fake.
اسم زوجها وزوجتها مع ماتسوي مزيف.
What?
لما؟
Don't worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن هذا
We can't run around like headless flies.
لا يمكننا الركض مثل الذباب مقطوع الرأس.
How about we go to the mansion Zhoushan Mansion
ماذا لو نذهب إلى قصر تشوشان القصر
The terrain of Zhoushan is complicated,
تضاريس تشوشان معقدة ،
We can still deal with them,
لا يزال بإمكاننا التعامل معهم ،
Okay,
تمام،
Yes.
نعم.
We can find Senior Jin Wuyi
يمكننا أن نجد جين وويى الكبير
and go to Mount Fuzhou.
والذهاب إلى جبل فوتشو.
Miaomiao, you're awake.
مياومياو ، أنت مستيقظ.
You're getting yourself into trouble.
أنت تضع نفسك في مشكلة.
You're making trouble for yourself.
أنت تسبب المتاعب لنفسك.
Pan Jun, keep an eye on our hostages.
بان جون ، راقب رهائننا.
Don't bother. I'm not trying to escape.
لا تهتم.  أنا لا أحاول الهروب.
Yan Yun, can you talk nicely?
يان يون ، هل يمكنك التحدث بلطف؟
Shut up!
اخرس!
We'll settle the accounts slowly.
سنقوم بتسوية الحسابات ببطء.
I know Yaxin has too many secrets.
أنا أعلم أن ياكسين لديه الكثير من الأسرار.
If you take me with you like this,
إذا أخذتني معك هكذا ،
you'll only put yourself in more danger.
ستعرض نفسك فقط لخطر أكبر.
Miaomiao,
مياومياو ،
didn't I tell you?
الم اخبرك
We can go to Mount Ba Men together,
يمكننا الذهاب إلى Mount Ba Men معًا ،
and find out what you want to know.
واكتشف ما تريد معرفته.
When the time comes, we'll open the Zerg treasure together.
عندما يحين الوقت ، سنفتح كنز الزرج معًا.
My father will come back.
سيعود والدي.
Yan Yun and Yan Ying's father will also come back.
سيعود أيضًا يان يون ووالد يان ينغ.
But the treasure must not
لكن الكنز لا يجب
fall into the wrong hands,
الوقوع في الأيدي الخطأ ،
The Yaxin Club wants to use someone
يريد نادي Yaxin استخدام شخص ما
as obsessed as you to open the treasure,
مهووس بفتح الكنز مثلك ،
They want to use the thousands of poisonous insects
يريدون استخدام آلاف الحشرات السامة
in the treasure to make weapons,
في الكنز لصنع الأسلحة ،
To create more disasters like pneumonic plague,
لخلق المزيد من الكوارث مثل الطاعون الرئوي ،
and when the bones turn into mountains,
وعندما تتحول العظام إلى جبال ،
They will support their troops and stand on their own feet,
سوف يدعمون قواتهم ويقفون على أقدامهم ،
so the culprit of pneumonic plague,
لذا فإن الجاني من الطاعون الرئوي ،
It's the Yaxin Club.
إنه نادي ياكسين.
I just found out about it.
انا فقط اكتشفته حديثا.
That's why I let you go.
لهذا السبب سمحت لك بالرحيل.
No way.
مستحيل.
There's no way ahead.
ليس هناك طريق إلى الأمام.
We have to make a detour
علينا القيام بالانعطاف
and get off on foot.
والنزول سيرا على الأقدام.
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
-Let's go. -Okay,
-هيا بنا.  -تمام،
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
-Hurry up. -Hurry up. I
-أسرع - بسرعة.  -أسرع - بسرعة.  أنا
can't do it anymore.
لا تستطيع أن تفعل ذلك بعد الآن.
Can I
هل استطيع
help you rest for a while?
تساعدك على الراحة لبعض الوقت؟
Take a break.
خذ استراحة.
I really can't do it anymore.
أنا حقا لا أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك بعد الآن.
Why are you standing there?
لماذا تقف هناك؟
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
Miaomiao.
مياومياو.
Yan Yun.
يان يون.
This is a secret treasure of the earth system.
هذا كنز سري لنظام الأرض.
Keep it safe for me.
احتفظ بها آمنة بالنسبة لي.
What are you doing,
ماذا تفعل،
bro? Don't come near me.
أخي؟  لا تقترب مني.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Master said,
قال المعلم ،
We must protect Shi Miaomiao,
يجب علينا حماية شي مياومياو ،
the descendant of the river system,
سليل نظام النهر ،
I'll tell you with my actions,
سأخبرك بأفعالي ،
Zerg,
زيرج ،
No one will betray
لن يخون أحد
Pan Jun,
بان جون ،
Yan Yun,
يان يون ،
take care.
يعتني.
Ziwu,
Ziu ،
trust me. I will definitely come back.
صدقني.  انا بلتأكيد سوف اعود.
I'm Ziwu.
أنا زيوو.
Don't worry,
لا تقلق،
Ziwu,
Ziu ،
I will definitely come back.
انا بلتأكيد سوف اعود.
Ziwu, come back.
Ziwu ، تعال.
It's too late.
لقد فات الأوان.
I believe he will come back.
أعتقد أنه سيعود.
It's an experiment.
إنها تجربة.
How dare you kidnap my people,
كيف تجرؤ على خطف شعبي ،
your people,
شعبك،
Listen carefully.
إستمع جيدا.
Shi Miaomiao
شي مياومياو
is a descendant of the Zerg Water System,
هو سليل نظام مياه الزرج ،
She's not your man,
انها ليست رجلك ،
and she's not Mrs. Matsui.
وهي ليست السيدة ماتسوي.
We're almost here.
نحن هنا تقريبا.
Ashin will not be familiar with the terrain here,
لن يكون "آشين" على دراية بالتضاريس هنا ،
so I think we should get rid of them.
لذلك أعتقد أننا يجب أن نتخلص منهم.
What about Ziwu?
ماذا عن Ziwu؟
Don't worry,
لا تقلق،
Ziwu will be fine.
سيكون Ziwu بخير.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
He has antibodies to the pneumonic plague,
لديه أجسام مضادة للطاعون الرئوي ،
and this time the northern Zhou pneumonic plague,
وهذه المرة الطاعون الرئوي في شمال تشو ،
Yaxin planned it.
ياكسين خطط لها.
Yaxin has been doing human experiments.
كان Yaxin يقوم بالتجارب البشرية.
Let go of me!
ترك لي!
Let me go back.
دعني أعود.
Ziwu.
إنها أغنية.
Yes,
نعم،
Ziwu is indeed their subject,
Ziwu هو بالفعل موضوعهم ،
I've seen the pinhole on his body before,
لقد رأيت الثقب على جسده من قبل ،
so I'm looking for Master's whereabouts,
لذلك أنا أبحث عن مكان للماجستير ،
He was also arrested by Yin-Yang Road.
كما تم اعتقاله من قبل طريق ين ويانغ.
Doing human experiments.
القيام بالتجارب البشرية.
Ziwu, as a descendant of the native land,
Ziwu ، باعتباره سليلًا من موطنه الأصلي ،
your AsiaInfo Club will not let him go.
لن يسمح له نادي AsiaInfo الخاص بك بالرحيل.
Although you said he had no worries for a while,
على الرغم من أنك قلت إنه ليس لديه مخاوف لفترة من الوقت ،
the experiments that destroyed human body,
التجارب التي دمرت جسم الإنسان ،
How can ordinary people stand it?
كيف يمكن للناس العاديين تحمل ذلك؟
Yan Yun
يان يون
Since Ziwu has made sacrifices for us,
منذ أن قدم Ziwu تضحيات من أجلنا ،
Ziwu has made sacrifices for us,
لقد قدم Ziwu تضحيات من أجلنا ،
We have to protect ourselves.
علينا حماية أنفسنا.
We can't let his sacrifice be meaningless.
لا يمكننا أن ندع تضحيته تكون بلا معنى.
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
Mr. Matsui,
السيد ماتسوي ،
Mr. Kim said,
قال السيد كيم ،
If the subject is alive,
إذا كان الموضوع على قيد الحياة ،
his life,
حياته،
More important than the entire Zerg.
أهم من الزرج كله.
Take him away.
يأخذه بعيدا.
Don't touch me.
لا تلمسني.
I can walk on my own.
يمكنني المشي بمفردي.
I'll take him with me.
سآخذه معي.
Who else do you want?
من ايضا تريد؟
Make yourself at home.
البيت بيتك.
Was that a gunshot?
هل كانت تلك طلقة نارية؟
I don't think
لا اعتقد
it's Yaxin's man, right?
إنه رجل ياكسين ، أليس كذلك؟
I wonder if Ziwu was caught by them.
أتساءل عما إذا كان Ziwu قد قبض عليهم.
You should be able to escape if you get caught.
يجب أن تكون قادرًا على الهروب إذا تم القبض عليك.
Once you escape, you can escape a second time.
بمجرد أن تهرب ، يمكنك الهروب مرة ثانية.
It's all because of someone.
كل هذا بسبب شخص ما.
Ziwu is sincere,
Ziwu صادق ،
and insists on listening to his master to protect you.
ويصر على الاستماع إلى سيده لحمايتك.
Even if I get caught, I can get away with it.
حتى لو تم القبض علي ، يمكنني أن أفلت من العقاب.
You don't have to worry about it.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن ذلك.
I think your ability to dig at me
أعتقد أن قدرتك على الحفر في وجهي
is much better than your ability to brag.
أفضل بكثير من قدرتك على التباهي.
You'd better speak louder.
من الأفضل أن تتحدث بصوت أعلى.
Tell Matsui to come
أخبر ماتسوي أن يأتي
and send us on the road early.
وأرسلنا على الطريق مبكرًا.
Sis,
الاخت ،
can we stop quarreling?
هل يمكننا التوقف عن الشجار؟
Focus on your feet,
ركز على قدميك ،
these are all traps made by hunters,
كل هذه الفخاخ صنعها الصيادون ،
Sister,
أخت،
Yan Ying,
يان ينغ ،
Yan Ying
يان ينغ
Brother Pan finally found you.
أخيرًا وجدك Brother Pan.
Yan Ying,
يان ينغ ،
you brat.
أنت شقي.
Where did it go?
اين ذهبت؟
Sister,
أخت،
who is this girl?
من هذة الفتاة؟
Her name is Xiao'e. She's a descendant of the Kim family.
اسمها Xiao'e.  إنها سليل عائلة كيم.
When we were chased by the Yaxin Club,
عندما طاردنا نادي ياكسين
fortunately, Miss Xiao'e saved us.
لحسن الحظ ، أنقذتنا الآنسة Xiao'e.
We just heard gunshots
سمعنا للتو طلقات نارية
and thought someone from the Yaxin Club was coming.
واعتقدت أن شخصًا ما من نادي Yaxin قادم.
I didn't expect it to be you.
لم أكن أتوقع أن تكون أنت.
You are.
أنت.
A member of the Kim family,
أحد أفراد عائلة كيم ،
Yes.
نعم.
Me
أنا
Kim Wu Yi is still alive.
كيم وو يي لا يزال على قيد الحياة.
This lady is so pretty,
هذه السيدة جميلة جدا
why does she speak so viciously?
لماذا تتكلم بقسوة؟
My master has always been strong,
كان سيدي قويًا دائمًا ،
and will only live longer than you.
وسيعيشون أطول منك فقط.
Miss Xiao'e,
ملكة جمال شياو ،
although this lady is a little more talkative,
على الرغم من أن هذه السيدة أكثر ثرثرة قليلاً ،
But we still get along very well.
لكننا ما زلنا على ما يرام.
Don't get me wrong.
لا تفهموني خطأ.
Who wants to get along with her?
من يريد أن يتعايش معها؟
Yan Ying,
يان ينغ ،
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
Mr. Jin,
السيد جين ،
welcome to Northern Zhou.
مرحبا بكم في نورثرن تشو.
Thank you for your hard work, Mr. Matsui.
شكرا لك على عملك الشاق ، سيد ماتسوي.
How is our experiment?
كيف هي تجربتنا؟
I've asked someone to take care of it.
لقد طلبت من شخص ما أن يعتني بها.
Mr. Jin, don't worry.
السيد جين ، لا تقلق.
This way, please.
من هنا لو سمحت.
Mr. Jin, this way, please.
سيد جين ، بهذه الطريقة ، من فضلك.
Excuse me,
عفوا،
how is Shangfeng?
كيف هو Shangfeng؟
Shangfeng is still in good health,
لا يزال Shangfeng في صحة جيدة ،
as long as his son doesn't make trouble,
طالما أن ابنه لا يسبب مشاكل ،
Even if the world is peaceful,
حتى لو كان العالم مسالمًا ،
how long are you going to stay this time?
كم ستبقى هذه المرة؟
After I confirm that the test body is safe,
بعد أن أؤكد أن جسم الاختبار آمن ،
next week,
الاسبوع القادم،
So I took him to Lingcheng with me.
لذلك أخذته معي إلى Lingcheng.
It's such a rush to go to the R & D center. I'm here
إنه لمن دواعي الاندفاع الذهاب إلى مركز البحث والتطوير.  أنا هنا
this time,
هذا الوقت،
Shangfeng has told you over and over again
أخبرك Shangfeng مرارًا وتكرارًا
that he is willing to give you 30% of the shares.
أنه على استعداد لمنحك 30٪ من الأسهم.
Second brother,
الأخ الثاني،
you will become the second largest shareholder of Yaxin Pharmaceutical.
ستصبح ثاني أكبر مساهم في Yaxin Pharmaceutical.
I can win Shangfeng's favor.
يمكنني الفوز لصالح Shangfeng.
Matsui is terrified?
ماتسوي مرعوب؟
Happy cooperation.
تعاون سعيد.
My pleasure.
من دواعي سروري.
Toyotomi Jun's lab
مختبر تويوتومي جون
uses Yersinia pestis for testing.
يستخدم اليرسينيا الطاعونية للاختبار.
In the afternoon when he was injected with Bacillus,
في فترة ما بعد الظهيرة عندما تم حقنه بالبكتيريا Bacillus ،
he ran all the way to the North Zhou Dynasty,
ركض على طول الطريق إلى أسرة تشو الشمالية ،
We caught him.
أمسكنا به.
He was lucky enough
كان محظوظا بما فيه الكفاية
to survive.
للبقاء على قيد الحياة.
The earth system has always tried medicine with its body,
لطالما جرب نظام الأرض الطب بجسمه ،
tasted all kinds of herbs,
تذوق جميع أنواع الأعشاب ،
It's immune to most strange poisons in the world.
إنه محصن ضد معظم السموم الغريبة في العالم.
That's why it became the carrier of plague.
لهذا السبب أصبحت حاملة الطاعون.
Fengchen Jun
Fengchen Jun
is really crazy.
هو حقا مجنون.
If you miss him,
إذا اشتقت إليه ،
you must catch him back.
يجب أن تعيده.
The super bacteria tested by Meridian
تم اختبار البكتيريا الفائقة بواسطة Meridian
will become the invincible product of Yaxin Pharmaceutical
سيصبح المنتج الذي لا يقهر من Yaxin Pharmaceutical
in the world in the future,
في العالم في المستقبل ،
We can attack everything.
يمكننا مهاجمة كل شيء.
Ziwu
إنها أغنية
is one of the keys to crack the Zerg treasure.
هو أحد مفاتيح كسر كنز الزرج.
I shouldn't be the victim of your experiment.
لا ينبغي أن أكون ضحية تجربتك.
Yes, yes.
نعم نعم.
I'm just saying it casually.
أنا فقط أقول ذلك بشكل عرضي.
Remember,
يتذكر،
evil comes from the mouth.
الشر يأتي من الفم.
Yes
نعم
Mr. Matsui,
السيد ماتسوي ،
this time,
هذا الوقت،
You must take strict care of him.
يجب أن تعتني به بدقة.
There can't be any more mishaps.
لا يمكن أن يكون هناك المزيد من الحوادث المؤسفة.
Miss Luo, don't worry.
آنسة لوه ، لا تقلق.
Call our doctor right away.
اتصل بطبيبنا على الفور.
Yes.
نعم.
Matsui Jun,
ماتسوي جون ،
you're done here.
لقد انتهيت هنا.
Yes.
نعم.
What else do you want?
ماذا تريد ايضا؟
I told you,
أخبرتك،
I don't have the earth secret treasure.
ليس لدي كنز الأرض السري.
No matter how hard you torture me, it's useless.
بغض النظر عن مدى صعوبة تعذيبي ، فهو عديم الفائدة.
If you want the treasure,
إذا كنت تريد الكنز ،
dream on.
في الحلم.
You have a big role to play.
لديك دور كبير لتلعبه.
I'll keep you safe.
سأبقيك آمنا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Me.
أنا.
I'm from Lingcheng,
أنا من Lingcheng ،
and I want to take you back to Lingcheng.
وأريد أن أعود بك إلى Lingcheng.
Lingcheng.
Lingcheng.
Fengchen Jun,
Fengchen Jun ،
I don't want to go back to that lab.
لا أريد العودة إلى ذلك المختبر.
I'm not going back to that lab.
لن أعود إلى هذا المختبر.
Let go of me!
ترك لي!
I'm not going back.
لن أعود.
Good-looking sister,
أخت حسن المظهر ،
why are you so careful
لماذا انت حريص جدا
when you want to come here?
متى تريد المجيء الى هنا؟
Secret treasure is such an important thing.
الكنز السري هو شيء مهم.
Why would I carry it with me?
لماذا أحملها معي؟
Of course I know that.
بالطبع أنا أعلم ذلك.
You don't have to tell me.
ليس عليك أن تخبرني.
You worry too much.
انت تقلق كثيرا.
I just want to take a look at this crabapple flower.
أريد فقط أن ألقي نظرة على زهرة الكرابابل هذه.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Although Xiao'e doesn't want to cause trouble,
على الرغم من أن Xiao'e لا يريد أن يسبب المشاكل ،
she really doesn't like to be sabotaged secretly.
إنها حقًا لا تحب أن يتم تخريبها سراً.
Please remember.
أرجوك تذكر.
Just call me Shi Miaomiao.
فقط اتصل بي شي مياومياو.
it seems
يبدو
You know exactly who I am.
أنت تعرف بالضبط من أنا.
Yan Yun and Yan Ying have warned me
حذرني يان يون ويان ينغ
to be careful.
أن نكون حذرين.
Besides, I'm also a descendant of the Zerg. In the past,
إلى جانب ذلك ، أنا أيضًا من نسل الزرج.  في الماضي،
all kinds of water systems,
جميع أنواع أنظمة المياه ،
I've heard a thing or two.
لقد سمعت شيئًا أو شيئين.
Of course I have to be wary of you.
بالطبع يجب أن أكون حذرا منك.
A word of caution,
كلمة تحذير،
this is Mount Fuzhou,
هذا جبل فوتشو
Please, Shi Miaomiao in the water system,
من فضلك ، شي مياومياو في نظام المياه ،
don't make trouble.
لا تجعل المتاعب.
He told me not to make trouble.
قال لي ألا أثير المشاكل.
Okay.
تمام.
Then ask your master to see me.
ثم اطلب من سيدك أن يراني.
Take it easy.
خذها ببساطة.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
You wanted to see me?
اردت رؤيتي؟
I'll come out.
سوف أخرج.
Why bother my disciple?
لماذا أزعج تلميذي؟
Grandpa,
الجد
Wu Yi,
وو يي ،
We haven't seen each other for more than 20 years.
لم نر بعضنا البعض منذ أكثر من 20 عامًا.
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Is there anything good about it?
هل هناك أي شيء جيد في ذلك؟
I'm just living with my life.
أنا فقط أعيش مع حياتي.
You look
أنت تبدو
just like Xiaoyu.
تمامًا مثل Xiaoyu.
But there's a lot more rage
لكن هناك الكثير من الغضب
between your eyebrows than your mother.
بين حاجبيك من والدتك.
In the battle of Mount Ba Men,
في معركة جبل با مين ،
as a gold gentleman,
كرجل نبيل ذهبي ،
Right at the scene.
الحق في مكان الحادث.
Yes,
نعم،
I watched your mother
لقد شاهدت والدتك
die,
موت،
In her death,
في وفاتها ،
all the gentlemen who were there were involved.
كل السادة الذين كانوا هناك كانوا متورطين.
It's a fact. I don't deny it.
انها حقيقة.  أنا لا أنكر ذلك.
But I didn't expect
لكني لم أتوقع
to see you today.
لأراك اليوم.
I'm not afraid of your revenge.
أنا لا أخاف من انتقامك.
I'm just worried,
أنا مجرد قلق،
The Water System has no
لا يوجد في نظام المياه
Empress. I see you today.
الإمبراطورة.  أراك اليوم.
I'm relieved.
أنا مرتاح.
Stop pretending.
كف عن التظاهر.
You want to wipe this place out?
تريد محو هذا المكان؟
It's not realistic.
إنه غير واقعي.
But if you want to find out
ولكن إذا كنت تريد معرفة ذلك
how your mother died?
كيف ماتت امك
Come with me then.
تعال معي بعد ذلك.
Mr. Jin, no problem.
السيد جين ، لا مشكلة.
Mr. Jin,
السيد جين ،
I didn't expect
لم أتوقع
anyone could hurt Lord Matsushige,
يمكن لأي شخص أن يؤذي اللورد ماتسوشيج ،
Hurry up and show it to Matsushita Jun,
اسرع واعرضه لماتسوشيتا جون ،
No need
لا حاجة
Thank you for your concern,
شكرا لاهتمامك،
boss. This injury is nothing.
رئيس.  هذه الإصابة لا شيء.
I was injured by this thing that day.
لقد أصبت بهذا الشيء في ذلك اليوم.
This is the Ghost of Gold,
هذا هو شبح الذهب ،
where is the person who hurt you?
اين الشخص الذي جرحك
He should still be in Mount Fuzhou,
يجب أن يظل في جبل فوتشو ،
but I fell into their trap by accident.
لكنني وقعت في فخهم بالصدفة.
Let Matsui go to Mount Fuzhou,
دع ماتسوي يذهب إلى جبل فوتشو ،
and you too. The sooner the better.
وانت ايضا.  عاجلا كان ذلك أفضل.
They're the only ones who know the secret treasure and its information.
هم الوحيدون الذين يعرفون الكنز السري ومعلوماته.
Remember,
يتذكر،
capture him alive,
قبض عليه حيا ،
Yes.
نعم.
Miaomiao,
مياومياو ،
you heard everything.
سمعت كل شيء.
It's my first time seeing Senior Jin,
إنها المرة الأولى التي أرى فيها سينيور جين ،
we can't collude with each other.
لا يمكننا أن نتآمر مع بعضنا البعض.
What he told me is exactly the same.
ما قاله لي هو نفسه بالضبط.
Miaomiao,
مياومياو ،
you must have been cheated.
لابد أنك تعرضت للغش.
Back then, all the gentlemen of the Five Clans
في ذلك الوقت ، كل السادة العشائر الخمس
were escorted.
تمت مرافقتهم.
Each of them was furious.
كان كل واحد منهم غاضبًا.
But after all, it was done by the Qing court.
لكن بعد كل شيء ، تم القيام به من قبل محكمة تشينغ.
If you resist,
إذا قاومت ،
One is a soldier of the Qing court,
أحدهم جندي في محكمة تشينغ ،
and the other is a thousand disciples of the Zerg,
والآخر ألف من تلاميذ الزرج.
In the end,
بالنهايه،
those innocent people will be hurt.
هؤلاء الأبرياء سوف يتأذون.
So,
لذا،
even if you don't want to,
حتى لو كنت لا تريد ذلك ،
We had no choice but to submit to humiliation.
لم يكن لدينا خيار سوى الخضوع للإذلال.
What's more,
ما هو أكثر من ذلك ،
Lord He of the Qing court is the in-laws of Ouyang family,
اللورد هو من محكمة تشينغ هو أصهار عائلة أويانغ ،
His daughter is the mother of Yan Ying and Yan Yun.
ابنته هي والدة يان ينغ ويان يون.
Second grandpa,
الجد الثاني
you only said that my mother is a sinner of the Zerg.
أنت فقط قلت أن أمي هي آثم الزرج.
But you never mentioned that
لكنك لم تذكر ذلك قط
she had so much to do with the Battle of Mount Ba Men,
كان لديها الكثير لتفعله في معركة جبل با مين ،
The enmity of the previous generation,
عداوة الجيل السابق ،
we don't want the lower generation to bear it,
لا نريد أن يتحمله الجيل الأدنى ،
But I have to
لكن لا بد لي من ذلك
tell you today.
أخبرك اليوم.
For thousands of years,
منذ آلاف السنين ،
the Zerg treasure has killed
قتل كنز الزرج
countless people in Bamen Mountain.
عدد لا يحصى من الناس في جبل بامين.
Although I have
على الرغم من أن لدي
never been there,
لم أكن هناك مطلقا،
But I know the road ahead is difficult and dangerous.
لكنني أعلم أن الطريق أمامنا صعب وخطير.
So,
لذا،
we decided not to come back.
قررنا عدم العودة.
When the gentlemen of the Five Clans
عند السادة العشائر الخمس
officially met,
التقى رسميا ،
Your mother told me.
قالت لي والدتك.
What did my mother say?
ماذا قالت والدتي؟
She said,
قالت ،
this trip
هذه الرحلة
It's extremely dangerous.
إنه أمر خطير للغاية.
Bamen Mountain is heavily defended,
جبل بامين محمي بشدة ،
and the Qing court is insidious and cunning,
ومحكمة تشينغ ماكرة وماكرة ،
I don't know its purpose.
لا أعرف الغرض منه.
If anything happens to her,
إذا حدث لها أي شيء ،
she'll be the first to stop her
ستكون أول من يوقفها
from sacrificing herself,
من التضحية بنفسها ،
He Luo Shi.
انه لوه شي.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Xiaoyu.
شياويو.
Xiaoyu has gone crazy,
لقد أصيب Xiaoyu بالجنون ،
and she won't kill anyone.
ولن تقتل أحدا.
The Zerg is over.
الزرج قد انتهى.
Saving the Zerg is here.
إنقاذ الزرج هنا.
Do you have the heart to see us destroy the clan?
هل لديك قلب لترانا ندمر العشيرة؟
Your mother also said,
قالت والدتك أيضا ،
"I hope all of us can protect ourselves. ",
"آمل أن نتمكن جميعًا من حماية أنفسنا." ،
You don't need to be soft-hearted.
لا تحتاج إلى أن تكون رقيق القلب.
I only hope that our water system will continue.
آمل فقط أن يستمر نظام المياه لدينا.
And I, the Zerg,
وأنا الزرج
have been safe for a long time.
كانت آمنة لفترة طويلة.